Yufan, have you finished reading those student files?
I've finished.
Sigh, these kids.
They're afraid the school will communicate with their parents,
so they are being secretive about this loan issue.
Isn't this just nonsense?
If they could solve this problem themselves,
why would we need to intervene?
But these students,
I don't know them either.
But rumor has it
that this lending started last year.
Ah.
You were the president of the student union at that time.
Don't you have any impression of these people?
When you were in the student union,
did you hear any rumors about loans?
Do you know how high the interest rate of this company's loan is?
We can't just leave our student union members
in the lurch, can we?
You are pushing him into the abyss.
Does he have the ability to pay back such high interest?
You're right. Then what should we do?
I will lend him my own money.
Don't worry.
If that's the case,
Hey, can those loan documents still be found?
Probably.
The borrower still has a copy.
Okay.
However,
just with these documents,
I still can't confirm
whether Wang Yu issued the loan.
I'll confirm it.
The teacher has found the loan company's info.
I'm worried they'll get my data from the company.
I've missed several payments.
The company threatened me before
that if I miss another payment,
they'll contact my family.
I'm worried they won't keep my info confidential.
How about this.
I'll find another platform for you.
You can borrow from there to tide yourself over.
Thank you.
If my mom finds out, she'll kill me.
This is the last student.
Are there any other companies that can lend to them?
Let's take some of our commission
and lend it to her.
That's the only way.
That's not just a little profit.
It means we did all this for nothing.
We could also raise the interest rate.
Then we'd make another killing.
But we have to collect it first.
Don't worry. Once we get back to the Student Union,
I have countless ways
to make her pay.
This is the loan contract Wang Yu brought out last year.
I think I've heard of this loan company.
Uncle He, can you look into it?
An investigation can only reveal the company's personnel and assets.
Getting evidence
that the Student Union leaked student data
is highly unlikely.
Can we pretend to be from the loan company
and ask Wang Yu for the student data?
Mhm.
They have designated contacts.
Asking for data right now would be too obvious.
It's fine if it's someone we haven't worked with before.
Then we'll pretend to be a new loan company
and contact them.
Why?
Xihai University's
student loans
were unexpectedly reported on a live broadcast.
Wang Yu definitely doesn't dare to contact the previous companies now.
Then they will be very short on money
and definitely need a new company to take over.
Yeah, that's highly possible.
This is the best solution for now.
I'll go contact someone.
Sorry for the trouble, Uncle He.
President.
A new loan company contacted us.
Are they reliable?
I asked around.
I heard they are quite reliable.
What are their requirements?
They want to verify the students' information with you in person.
We are miles apart.
How can I give it to him?
They will come over.
They said the manager happens to be in town these days.
What a coincidence. OPE TO THE E.
Ah.
It's much more reliable than lending out our own money.
President.
Even if we wanted to lend it out ourselves,
with so many students in debt,
how could we ever cover it all?
Did you agree on where to meet?
Not yet.
Didn't An Yufan arrange to meet him today?
Why is there no movement at all?
I didn't expect him to meet here.
Wouldn't it be better to just record it?
Why do we have to livestream it?
I'm not sure.
But Zixi wanted to livestream it.
She must have her reasons.
By the way,
did you communicate clearly with the teacher?
We did.
The internet isn't working here.
The IP is occupied, and the livestream port is blocked.
Did they set this up in advance?
Are you done?
It's almost time.
Hello, Mr. He.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Are you the student council president?
The president has other matters to attend to, so I will be liaising with you.
Did you bring the information on the students taking out loans?
Take a look.
I was wondering
who was following me.
What a coincidence. Why are you here too?
What are you doing here?
I should be asking you that.
I was just curious about what happened.
If there's nothing else, I'll be leaving now.
It's not good to take someone else's things.
Let me go.
Let go!
You set up those student loans, didn't you?
You meddle too much.
You know their parents
worked so hard to pay for their education,
only for them to return with a mountain of debt.
Do you know how devastated they will be?
They deserve it.
You took huge profit cuts from their loans
and forced them to take out new loans to pay off old ones.
How can you even say that?
I earned it.
I work for my commissions.
What about the students who didn't want a loan in the first place?
They didn't ask for your loans.
That's because I'm good at my job.
You're actually proud of being shameless.
Are you complimenting me?
Thanks.
Anything else you want to say?
But time is running out.
Do you know that your files
have already been found by An Yufan?
You'd better turn yourself in right now.
You mean
the ones Huiying brought over?
Mine aren't in there.
Mine are all here.
Why? Are you unwilling to give up?
Do you still want to guard this pile of documents?
Then don't blame me
for being impolite.
An Yufan.
Thank you for your confession.
What you just said
has been broadcast live by me.
Wang Yu, you have failed the school's trust in you.
Take him away.
Why didn't you wait for me?
I saw he hadn't taken the bait,
so I rushed in anxiously.
Thank you.
Deputy Actor Director: Xi Chongjing.
Props Assistant: Li Kunxiao.
Field Vehicle: Yi Mingle,
Yi Tong.